http://www.mosoap.com/pages/privacy-policy

We are open and shipping for $6 flat rate in the USA!
MoSoap®'s Privacy Policy
The following is the privacy policy for the MoSoap® web site. In this policy, we describe what personal information we collect on our site, how we use it, and your options regarding information we may collect about you. This Privacy Policy covers the information you provide to us off-line and at the MoSoap® Web site (www.mosoap.com). We do this to demonstrate our commitment to our users’ privacy, and we disclose the following information.1. What personally identifiable information MoSoap® collects.2. What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the Web site.3. What organization collects the information.4. How MoSoap® uses the information.5. With whom MoSoap® may share user information.6. What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.7. What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under MoSoap®'s control.8. How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information.Cookies A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. You can set your browser to notify you to either accept or deny the cookie according to the following information. We use a session cookie called botanicalearth.com -most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually refuse cookies, or selectively accept cookies, by adjusting the preferences in your browser. This cookie only stores information related Users have the option to participate in this activity for the purpose of contacting by email or regular mail. A user must provide the clickstream information (internet protocol address, internet service provider, platform type, date/time stamp, operating system), http protocol information (last url requested and browser type), computer information (computer and browser information), content (email content and bulletin board postings), navigation and click-stream data (passive activity such as pages visited), purchase information (purchase payment method and other purchase information), state management mechanisms (data allowing a user to be tracked consistently), search terms (search text), transaction information (account transactions), user's name, user's login information, user's home contact information and user's business contact information. The reason we use this information is to complete the current transaction, contact by email or regular mail, enhance our site and product offerings, maintain and secure our site and understand (in aggregate) interests of website visitors. We retain this information as stated by our business practices.Our website uses cookies to enhance our site. Profiles MoSoap does not create a user profile.Communications from the Site When customers provide us contact information for User Group 1 (user participation is voluntary) we use the information to contact the user to deliver sales and product information that will be useful to the them.Sharing Information - Legal Disclaimer Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. Personally Identifiable Information Personally identifiable information is not shared with any third parties.Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)Aggregate information is not shared with any third parties.Data Security MoSoap® has physical security in our facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information. Our company uses secure encryption technology (secure socket connection) for all sensitive financial or health data transmitted on our site.Visitors Under 13 Years of Age Though we are a family friendly site, MoSoap® does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information online from a child under 13 since our site is not directed at children.Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address) they can change this information online, physical contact, and other information. If a user wishes to correct/update information or no longer desires our service, they can notify us of what they desire by contacting us using any of the information in the Contact section of this policy.Links and Advertisements Our website contains links to other sites. We have partnerships with ad server companies. We, MoSoap®, are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.Changes to the Privacy Statement The information you submit to us is controlled by the privacy policy in effect at the time you submit it. Changes made to this policy will be effective 14 days following the posting of the new policy on the Web site. If we make significant changes to our data handling practices, we will make efforts to notify our active customers in other reasonable ways that may include an administrative email or a post a notice in a conspicuous place on our website notifying visitors of policy changes. This privacy policy will be governed by the laws of the United States and the State of Missouri.Data Retention Statement Stated Business Practices Data retention - We keep information about you and your purchases for as long as you remain our customer. If you do not place an order from us for one year we will remove your information from our main databases.Legal Requirement Data Retention We retain transaction data for up to 5 years . Stated Purpose Data retention - We retain transaction data for up to 5 years.Resolving Privacy Policy Disputes If you think we have not followed our privacy policy in some way, please contact us immediately with your concerns and we will address them in a timely manner.
